udownloadsoft.com 2014-04-23

# Software and Driver Updates - udownloadsoft.com

Privacy Policy 

udownloadsoft.com (“We” or “uDownloadSoft”) know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and We take your privacy seriously.

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) and other information We gather when you are accessing our website at[http://www.udownloadsoft.com](http://www.udownloadsoft.com/) (the “Site”).

In addition, this Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of Personal Information and other information We gather when you use any of our services or products, including the wrapper installation utility.

By visiting the Site, or using any of our services or products, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

Please note this policy does not apply to (and We are not responsible for) the practices of companies that We do not own or control or to individuals We do not employ or manage. When utilizing third party sites or software products, you should read the relevant privacy policies of those third parties for information regarding their privacy practices.

1\. SUMMARY OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy pertains to the udownloadsoft.com Site and to the products and services available through the Site. To better explain what information We collect, and how We use the information We collect, We have broken out our Privacy Policy into the following sections:

Section 2: WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY. This section explains what information We collect from:

(a) visitors to the Site;

(b) users who download third party software that utilizes our installer utility

(c) users who install or use third party software, websites links or services; and

(d) users who receive software recommendations.

Section 3: HOW WE SHARE OR USE INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED. This section explains how We use your information, and why, as well as if and how We share your information.

Sections 4-8: These sections discuss various topics, including how We protect any information We collect, how you can update any information you share with us, our compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, our storage and use of information from users outside the United States, and how We may alert you of any changes to this Privacy Policy.

2\. WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY

a. VISITORS TO OUR SITE

If you are a visitor to our Site, We collect the following types of information:

Cookies. When you visit our Site We will send your browser a cookie which is stored in your browser and allows us to uniquely identify it. We use cookies to help us better understand our users and our product which allows us to improve our service. This data may include storing user preferences and product utilization information such as number of visitors, average time spent on pages, features used, and other information which helps us determine which features are most important to you and working effectively.

Logs. When you visit our Site We capture and store the data that your browser sends us. This data may include your browser type, language, Internet Protocol address, the date and time of your request and the cookie that helps us identify your unique browser.

Usage Information. Generally, our Site automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and its components. We only use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of our Site or services so that We can improve our Site and services.

Communication Anytime you send us a communication We may keep this communication so that We can respond to your requests or inquiries and help improve our services to you.

Information You Provide. We also receive and store any information you enter on our Site or provide to us in any other way, including information you may provide to us to create a user account. The types of Personal Information collected when you create a user account may include your name, user name and email address. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as customizing and improving our services, and communicating with you about specials and new features.

Third Party Software, Applications, Websites, Advertisements, Links and Services. uDownloadSoft may allow third party software and applications, as well as links to third party websites and services (“Third Party Services”), to be offered or made available by third parties not affiliated with uDownloadSoft (“Third Party Providers”), through the Site or its services. The Site may also contain advertisements that link to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that Third Party Provider’s website.

This Privacy Policy only applies to our Site and services. We do not exercise control over any websites that our Site, or that a third party application, may link to. These other applications, websites, links or services may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Information collected by such third parties, including information collected through links to social media sites, is governed by the third party privacy policies of those applications, websites, links or services. In addition, the fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement of such Third Party Provider’s privacy or information security policies or practices. We recommend that you read the privacy policies, terms of use or end user license agreements of the other websites you visit.

b. USERS WHO INSTALL THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE USING THE  INSTALLATION UTILITY

If you are a user who has downloaded and installed third party software, or have clicked on or use third party websites, links and services:

uDownloadSoft may allow Third Party Services to be offered or made available by Third Party Providers, through the Site or its services. This Privacy Policy only applies to our Site and services. We do not exercise control over any Third Party Services that our Site, or that a third party application, may link to or access.

These Third Party Services may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Information collected by Third Party Providers, including information collected through links to social media sites, is governed by the privacy policies of such Third Party Providers for such Third Party Services. When utilizing Third Party Services, we recommend that you should read the relevant terms of use regarding use of such third party websites, software or products, including any applicable privacy policies, terms of use and end user license agreements.

d. USERS WHO RECEIVE SOFTWARE RECOMMENDATIONS

If you are a user receiving recommendations for Third Party Software through the OpenCandy Network or other software recommendation networks:

Third party software available for download or installation from the Site may, as part of the download or installation process, provide for further recommendations of third party software through the AVG Software Recommendation Network or other third party software recommendation networks (“Recommendation Services”). Such recommendation services may collect information as part of the download or installation process. Information collected by the AVG Software Recommendation Network is governed by the AVG Privacy Policy, which may be found at <http://www.avg.com/ww-en/privacy>.

3\. HOW WE SHARE OR USE INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED

For all Personal Information and other information We collect, we may share or use such information as follows:

Protection of uDownloadSoft and Others.

We may share your Personal Information and other information if We have a good faith belief that it is required to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (3) enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy and/or any other agreements between you and uDownloadSoft, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of uDownloadSoft, its visitors, users and/or the public.

Business Transfers. If uDownloadSoft or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that uDownloadSoft goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. Accordingly, We may transfer or assign all the information We have collected as part of a merger, acquisition, sale or other change of control. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror may continue to use your Personal Information and other information as set forth in this policy.

Non-Personal Information. We may share your non-personally identifiable information with partners and other third parties for the purpose of helping us improve our recommendations and the overall performance of our service. For example, We may utilize data to determine the probability that a consumer will enjoy a specific product.

With Your Consent. Except as set forth above, We will only share your Personal Information with third parties with your prior consent.

4\. INFORMATION SECURITY

We endeavor to take security measures to guard against unauthorized access to the systems where We store your data. This includes internal reviews of our data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures and physical security measures. However, despite the measures We take We cannot warrant the security of any information provided to us. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

5\. UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

Through the process provided on our sites, We allow you to access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. The types of information that you can access and update will change as our sites change. You may request deletion of your uDownloadSoft account by sending an email to contact@udownloadsoft.com and responding affirmatively to any confirmation emails that We may send. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

6\. CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT

In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), We will not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and guardians to be familiar with the web sites that their children visit. The Federal Trade Commission (“FTC”) regulates the collection and use of personal information from children under 13, pursuant to COPPA. For more information you may visit the FTC’s website at[www.ftc.gov/privacy](http://www.joydownload.com/www.ftc.gov/privacy).

7\. USERS LOCATED OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES

Our Site, services and products are hosted by servers located in the United States. If you are located outside the United States, your information will be transferred to our servers in the United States. By visiting our Site, or using any of our services or products, you consent to the transfer, storage and use of your information in the United States.

8\. POLICY CHANGES

We may make changes to this policy from time to time. If We make changes in the way We use Personal Information, We will notify you by posting an announcement on our site or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses our site or services after such changes have been first posted.
